upsellit.com 2019-12-25

# UpSellit Privacy Policy

USI Technologies, Inc., DBA UpSellit.com has created this Privacy Policy Statement in order to inform you of our commitment to privacy and to describe our policies for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by USI when you visit our websites or interact with certain USI marketing engagements. USI’s partner websites may contain additional privacy policies. Your visits to those sites will be governed by the privacy policies, if any, that govern those sites.

PLEASE REVIEW THIS PRIVACY POLICY BEFORE USING THIS MARKETING ENGAGEMENT. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY, DO NOT USE THE MARKETING ENGAGEMENT. BY SUBMITTING ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE MARKETING ENGAGEMENT, YOU AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT.

IP Addresses and Cookies

Upsellit does not collect, retain, or share end user information including IP addresses, unique user identifiers, or personally identifiable information from sites or apps not owned by Upsellit (Third Party Websites).

Generally speaking, you may visit the partner site while remaining anonymous and not revealing any personal information.

Our marketing engagements automatically log your IP address and domain name, and non-personal information such as the type of web browser you use, to help us administer the marketing engagements and to compile statistics such as the number of visitors.

Our marketing engagements use cookies to identify you over multiple visits to the site, for example to remember your country and provide country-specific content. Cookies are optional, and you can block or delete them. However, some parts of our marketing engagementswill not work without cookies. Cookies may also be used to track visitor behavior on the website, which allows visitors to be retargeted with marketing engagements that reflects their past behavior on the site.

## **SUBMISSION OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Certain portions of the marketing engagements may require that you submit some personal information, such as your name and email address, before using those portions of the site. For some services, you may have to create an account, and submit additional personal information such as your mailing address.

## **USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

USI uses information it collects to provide the services and information you select, to better understand its customers, to provide better products and services, and to assist with site administration, such as with troubleshooting any problems, detecting fraud, resolving disputes, and for any purposes deemed necessary or required by USI to enforce the Terms of Use and other terms or conditions applicable to any portion of the site.

We also use this information to send you information about USI, or other topics USI thinks may be of interest to you, such as product information or updates. As part of its business, USI works with authorized partners to provide you with the services and information. As part of those activities, USI may share your information with those authorized entities so that they can directly provide the information or services to you.

* * *

## **SMS MARKETING**

By providing your contact information you provide clear, expressed consent to receiving information on products, sales, and promotions via SMS / text message. Consent is not a requirement to the purchase of goods or services. You may opt-out at any time by replying "STOP" to any message that you receive and you may request additional assistance by replying "HELP". After opting out, you may again opt-in to receiving communications by replying START. You may receive 5 messages per month.

Note to T-Mobile customers: T-Mobile is not liable for delayed or undelivered messages. Message and Data Rates May Apply.

## **AGGREGATION AND USE OF ANONYMOUS DATA**

USI aggregates information provided by you to create anonymous statistical and demographic data. This anonymous data helps USI to understand and know its customer base better. That anonymous data may be provided to third parties but never in such a fashion as to identify you personally.  Some USI products use Google Analytics for the collection of anonymous data. Learn more about how Google uses data collected using Google Analytics.  

## **THIRD PARTIES**

USI does not sell to third parties information you have submitted to this site that identifies you personally.  
On occasion, USI may offer in conjunction with third parties certain services that may require you to share your personal information with that third party as a condition for receiving that service. While USI will treat any information it receives in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement, USI will not be responsible for the information submitted by you to that third party, and we remind you to review the applicable rules and any third party's applicable privacy policies separately before participating in such service. Third party vendors may also use cookies to serve digital ads based on a person’s past visits to the USI site.

## **DECLINING INFORMATION**

You can opt out of receiving USI marketing messages; see the Accept/Decline section below. Please note that it may take us a reasonable amount of time to process your request.  
Even if you decline to receive information or cancel your account, USI reserves the right to use the information you previously provided to provide you with the USI products and services you are eligible to receive and to contact you about administrative matters relating to your use of any portion of the site, your account, or about any issues relating to the Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy, or any other policy then in-effect.

## **USI LINKS TO OTHER SITES AND ADVERTISING**

This site may display advertisements and/or links to third parties. USI is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those websites. Please refer to that company's privacy policy for further information.

## **SURVEYS**

From time to time USI may make online surveys available to users of the site. Participation in those surveys is voluntary. Some online surveys may ask participants for personal information, such as an email address, in addition to requesting answers to survey questions. USI may use that personal information to contact the participant if necessary, or as otherwise described above. USI may make the results of any survey publicly available, although USI will not attribute any particular response to you without your permission.

We do not wish to receive data from children. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the sites their children visit. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, USI’s website by visitors under 18 years of age without the consent of their parent or guardian. For sites that are intended for use by children we have put in place additional privacy practices which are described on those sites.  

## **GENERAL ISSUES**

Generally speaking, this site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. No security measures are 100% effective and USI does not warrant the security of your personal information.  Since the site under general usage does not collect financial information, USI uses the standard internet connections for those general usage portions of the site, without secured sockets.

## **SPECIFIC SERVICES**

This site may provide certain additional, optional services that may use additional security measures to protect the information, such as financial information, provided by you to obtain the service. Those additional security measures may vary, depending upon the particular service offered. You will be informed of any specific security measures at the time you register for a particular service. Please review that information for further detail.

If and when USI makes changes to this site and its products and services, USI may have to update this Privacy Policy Statement to better reflect those changes. Because changes to this site or updates to this Privacy Policy Statement may occur, you should review this Privacy Policy Statement from time to time. Remember, your decision to continue using this site after this Privacy Policy Statement is updated will signify that you have agreed to any new terms.

Typically you accept to receive communications when you submit information to a marketing engagement. If you wish to remove your information from the site database and no longer want to receive future communications, you may do so through the method described below. Please note that it may take us a reasonable amount of time to process your request.

  1. You can send an email to **hello@upsellit.com** for assistance in deleting/changing your prior selections.

  2. You can click the ‘delete my data’ button located in the footer of USI’s emails.

## **CORRECT / UPDATE**

USI gives users the following option for changing and modifying information previously provided.

  1. You can send an email to hello@upsellit.com for assistance in deleting/changing your prior selections.

## **CONTACTING THE WEB SITE**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact the Manager at the following address and email:

Manager, Website Strategy & Operations

USI Technologies, Inc.

29219 Canwood St, Suite 230

Agoura Hills, CA 91301

U.S.A

**hello@upsellit.com**

## **NOTICE TO EUROPEAN USERS**

Please note that the information you enter on the site or otherwise provide to USI Technologies, or its subsidiaries or divisions, may be transferred outside of the European Economic Area, for purposes of processing, by USI Technologies, Inc. a company located in Agoura Hills, California, U.S.A., or its subsidiaries or USI's subsidiaries or divisions, or authorized partners, located worldwide, in order to provide this site and its services to you. You are advised that the United States uses a sectoral model of privacy protection that relies on a mix of legislation, governmental regulation, and self-regulation. You are further advised that the Council of the European Union has found that this model does not provide "adequate" privacy protections as contemplated by Article 25 of the European Union's Data Directive. (Directive 95/46/EC, 1995 O.J. (L 281) 31)

USI maintains full compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). Article 44 GDPR allows for transfer of personal data to a third country or to an international organization if the provisions of GDPR are complied with by the data controller and processor.

By agreeing to this Policy, you consent to the transfer of all such information to the United States and the processing of that information as described in this Policy
